http://www.babcockpower.com/privacy-policy/

BPI Businesses
Babcock Power Environmental
Babcock Power Services
Boiler Tube Company of America (BTA)
BTA IMTEC Door
GSI
Riley Power
Struthers Wells
Thermal Engineering International (TEi)
TEiC Construction Services
TEiC Heat Exchanger Services (TEiC HX)
Babcock Power Services
Boiler Tube Company of America (BTA)
BTA IMTEC Door
GSI
Riley Power
Struthers Wells
Thermal Engineering International (TEi)
TEiC Construction Services
TEiC Heat Exchanger Services (TEiC HX)
Privacy Policy
This website is operated by Babcock Power Inc. headquartered out of Danvers, MA. Babcock Power Inc. and its associated companies will use the information we collect from you in accordance with this policy. Babcock Power Inc. (“we”, or “us”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
Babcock Power Inc. has made reasonable efforts to ensure that the information provided on this website is accurate at the time of inclusion. However, there may be unintentional and occasional errors for which Babcock Power Inc. apologizes. Babcock Power Inc. makes no representations, warranties, or assurances of any kind as to the accuracy, currency or completeness of the information provided. Babcock Power Inc. shall not be liable for any damages or injury resulting from your access to, or inability to access, this website, or from your reliance on any information provided at this website.
Please note that the documents and information available on this website are provided as a service only and are not the official versions of Babcock Power Inc. disclosure documents as required by any applicable securities, financial services, company law or any other legal requirements. In addition, website content may not always be the most current source for company information.
This website may contain links or references to other internet sites maintained by third parties. Babcock Power Inc. makes no representations, warranties or assurances as to any information in such sites and has no responsibility for their content, accuracy, currency or completeness and shall not be liable for any damages or injury arising from that content, accuracy, currency or completeness. Any links to other sites are provided merely as a convenience to the users of this website.
The trademarks, services marks, trade names, trade dress and products represented on this website are protected internationally. No use of these may be made without prior, written authorization of Babcock Power Inc. except to identify the products or services of the company.
Any communications you send to this website or otherwise to Babcock Power Inc. by electronic mail are on a non-confidential basis, and Babcock Power Inc. is under no obligation to refrain from reproducing, publishing or otherwise using them in any way or for any purpose. Babcock Power Inc. shall be free to use the content of any such communication, including any ideas, inventions, concepts, techniques or know-how disclosed therein, for any purpose including developing, manufacturing and/or marketing goods and services.
The sender of communications to this website or otherwise to Babcock Power Inc. shall be responsible for the content and information contained therein, including its truthfulness and accuracy.
This website is provided as a service to its visitors. Babcock Power Inc. reserves the right to delete, modify or supplement the content of this site at any time for any reason without notification to anyone.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
By submitting information to Babcock Power Inc. by means of facilities provided on this website you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information in accordance with the terms of this policy.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Information provided to Babcock Power Inc. by users of this site (“data subjects”) is stored electronically and securely and is not accessible by third parties.
We may use your information to contact you by post, telephone or email to let you know about other products and services we offer that may be of interest to you, to seek your views on our products and services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to them or to the site.
We will NOT disclose your information to any third party. Any changes to this privacy policy will be clearly notified on this website.
Cookies
Cookies are files sent by web servers to web browsers that enable a web server to identify and track these web browsers whenever the browser requests information from the server.
Babcock Power Inc. uses Google Analytics to collect information about how people use our site. We do this to ensure the site is functional in meeting its users’ needs and to give us an understanding on how we can improve our site.
Google Analytics stores information about the pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. We do not collect or store any personal information so this data cannot be used to identify who you are. We do not allow Google to use or share our analytics data. You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy at the following link:
https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners
You can refuse to accept cookies in most browsers by locating the cookie settings. Disabling cookies can restrict the usability of some websites.
Legal Disclosures
Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your personal data in response to valid requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to amend this privacy statement from time to time consistent with Privacy Shield’s requirements.
Babcock Power Inc.
Start typing and press Enter to search
